winthrillsnetwork.com 2018-12-20

# WINThrills Network - Privacy Policy

We take your privacy very seriously. Please read this privacy policy carefully as it contains important information on who we are and how and why we collect, store, use and share your personal information. It also explains your rights in relation to your personal information and how to contact us or supervisory authorities in the event you have a complaint. 

We collect, use and are responsible for certain personal information about you. When we do so we are subject to the General Data Protection Regulation, which applies across the European Union (including in the United Kingdom) and we are responsible as ‘controller’ of that personal information for the purposes of those laws.

Personal information we collect about you

We may collect and use the following personal information about you:

  * your name and contact information, including email address and telephone number
  * information to enable us to check and verify your identity, e.g. your date of birth
  * your gender information, if you choose to give this to us
  * location data, from your IP location and also if you choose to give this to us personnaly
  * your billing information, transaction and payment card information
  * your personal or professional interests
  * your contact history, purchase history and saved items
  * information from accounts you link to us, e.g. Facebook
  * information to enable us to undertake credit or other financial checks on you
  * information about how you use our website, IT, communication and other systems
  * your responses to surveys, competitions and promotions

This personal information is required to provide products and services to you. If you do not provide personal information we ask for, it may delay or prevent us from providing products and services to you.

How your personal information is collected

We collect most of this personal information directly from you—in person, by telephone, text or email and/or via our website forms online. However, we may also collect information:

  * from publicly accessible sources, eg Companies House or HM Land Registry;
  * directly from a third party, eg:

  1. sanctions screening providers;
  2. credit reference agencies;
  3. customer due diligence providers;
  4. marketing agencies and lead generation companies

  * from a third party with your consent, e.g. sub agency, lawyers, business associates
  * from cookies on our website — for more information on our use of cookies, please see our cookies policy
  * via our IT systems, eg:

  1. door entry systems and reception logs;
  2. automated monitoring of our websites and other technical systems, such as our computer networks and connections, CCTV and access control systems, communications systems, email and instant messaging systems;

How and why we use your personal information

Under data protection law, we can only use your personal information if we have a proper reason for doing so, eg:

  * to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations;
  * for the performance of our contract with you or to take steps at your request before entering into a contract;
  * for our legitimate interests or those of a third party; or
  * where you have given consent

A legitimate interest is when we have a business or commercial reason to use your information, so long as this is not overridden by your own rights and interests. 

Promotional communications

We may use your personal information to send you updates (by email, text message, telephone or post) about our products AND/OR services, including exclusive offers, promotions or new products AND/OR services.

We have a legitimate interest in processing your personal information for promotional purposes (see above ‘How and why we use your personal information’). This means we do not usually need your consent to send you promotional communications. However, where consent is needed, we will ask for this consent separately and clearly.

We will always treat your personal information with the utmost respect and never sell OR share it with other organisations save for completion of a investment on your behalf

You have the right to opt out of receiving promotional communications at any time by:

  * contacting us at info@winthrillsnetwork.com
  * updating your marketing preferences on our online preference centre

###### Your rights

You have the following rights, which you can exercise free of charge:

Access | The right to be provided with a copy of your personal information (the right of access)  
---|---  
Rectification | The right to require us to correct any mistakes in your personal information  
To be forgotten | The right to require us to delete your personal information—in certain situations  
Restriction of processing | The right to require us to restrict processing of your personal information—in certain circumstances, eg if you contest the accuracy of the data  
Data portability | The right to receive the personal information you provided to us, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and/or transmit that data to a third party—in certain situations  
To object | The right to object:

  * at any time to your personal information being processed for direct marketing (including profiling);
  * in certain other situations to our continued processing of your personal information, eg processing carried out for the purpose of our legitimate interests.

###### Keeping your personal information secure

We have appropriate security measures to prevent personal information from being accidentally lost, or used or accessed unlawfully. We limit access to your personal information to those who have a genuine business need to access it. Those processing your information will do so only in an authorised manner and are subject to a duty of confidentiality.

We also have procedures in place to deal with any suspected data security breach. We will notify you and any applicable regulator of a suspected data security breach where we are legally required to do so.

If you want detailed information from Get Safe Online on how to protect your information and your computers and devices against fraud, identity theft, viruses and many other online problems, please visit [www.getsafeonline.org](http://experienceinvest.com/privacy/www.getsafeonline.org). Get Safe Online is supported by HM Government and leading businesses.

###### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

###### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

Changes to this privacy policy

This privacy notice was published on 30th May 2018 and last updated on 30th May 2018   
We may change this privacy notice from time to time
